buzzslate.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy - BuzzSlate

## What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”), and other information described in this policy, gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications, such as Facebook (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Service. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

## What Information Do We Collect?

The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect, use, share, and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of information from our users.

### ACCOUNT INFORMATION:

When you create an Account, you will provide information, such as your username, password and email address. If you access the Services through Facebook credentials, we may automatically collect certain information, such as your name, picture, and email address. We will use all information available through Facebook in accordance with Facebook’s policies and your preferences selected through Facebook. As permitted by law, we may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, when we feel such information is important. You may unsubscribe from these messages through your Account settings, although we reserve the right to contact you even if you unsubscribe when we believe it is necessary in connection with the Services, such as for Account recovery purposes.

### USER CONTENT:

Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments. The Services are designed to help you share such content with others. As a result, some of the provided content is shared publicly or with third parties. Therefore, all content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us for as long as we require it in relation to the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, subject to state law, even after you terminate your Account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties, as described in this Privacy Policy.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY:

We automatically receive and record information from your device or web browser when you interact with the Services. This information may include, your IP address, an ID that we may create and associate with our content, cookie information, and other details. This information is used for fighting spam/malware, to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services (e.g., what links you have clicked on and shared with others, including via email and social media), and to otherwise personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. We may associate the information we collect by automated means with your Account if you have one, the device you use to connect to the Services, or email or social media accounts that you use to share our content.

Generally, the Services automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site or mobile application. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them.

When you visit the Site, we may also collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. Because there is not yet a consensus on how companies should respond to web browser-based or other do-not- track (“DNT”) mechanisms, we do not respond to web browser-based DNT signals at this time.

Please see our Cookies Policy for more detail about the information we may collect automatically and your choices.

### LOCATION DATA:

Some of our Services, such as mobile applications, may collect geo- location data (which determines your current location) to provide location- related Service functionality. We may link location data to other information we have collected about you for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. You may stop sharing your location data by adjusting your mobile device’s location services settings. For instruction on changing the relevant settings, please contact your service provider or device manufacturer.

### EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS:

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our Services, including customer service.

### INFORMATION RELATED TO ADVERTISING:

To support and enhance the Services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. We may engage with ad networks that are members or organizations or programs that manage the advertising privacy choices these ad networks offer consumers.

When you visit our Site or other Services, ad networks and other parties may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these ad networks and other parties.

Advertisements served through the Services may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category, which may be inferred from information provided to us by a user, may be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. We do not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use other than in connection with the Services.

### AGGREGATE INFORMATION:

We collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information.

## How, and With Whom, Is My Information Shared?

The Services are designed to help you share information with others. As a result, some of the information generated through the Services is shared publicly or with third parties.

We do not sell or otherwise disclose Personal Information we collect about you, except as described in this Privacy Policy or as we notify you at the time we collect the information.

### PUBLIC INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR ACTIVITY ON THE SERVICES:

Some of your activity on and through the Services is public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, content you have posted or shared publicly on the Site or otherwise through the Services, such as written posts, comments, or other submissions by you to the Site.

Registered users may have some of this information associated with their Accounts. In addition, information concerning the use of the Services (such as what pages they have visited) by unregistered users may be tracked through the use of cookies and other automated data collection means, and stored by us.

Please also remember that by choosing to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, you make your information publicly available. Users reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through the Services.

### IP ADDRESS INFORMATION:

We may share limited IP address information with our partners, service providers and other entities with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

### AGGREGATE INFORMATION:

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

### EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS WITH US:

As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us, such as communications relating to your Account. Communications relating to your Account will be sent for purposes important to the Services, such as password recovery. We may use your email address to contact you for editorial purposes, to advise you of any changes to our Site, and to send you messages about our marketing partners’ products with your consent or as permitted by law. You may choose not to receive our marketing emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails you receive from us, or by updating your preferences in your Account settings. Please note that even if you opt out, we may continue sending you service-related information.

### USER PROFILE INFORMATION:

User profile information including your username and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services. We will not reveal user email addresses to other users of the Site.

### INFORMATION SHARED WITH OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS:

We employ and contract with service providers – individuals and entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf. We may need to share Personal Information with our service providers in order to provide products or services to you. We request that our service providers use Personal Information or other information we share with them solely for the purpose to assist us.

### INFORMATION DISCLOSED PURSUANT TO BUSINESS TRANSFERS:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information, including Personal Information, is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur as permitted by law. Following the transfer of user information in the circumstances described in this paragraph, all inquiries concerning the processing of user information should be directed to the entity to which the information is transferred.

### INFORMATION DISCLOSED FOR OUR PROTECTION AND THE PROTECTION OF OTHERS:

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce our User Agreement, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

### INFORMATION WE SHARE WITH YOUR CONSENT:

In addition to the types of sharing Personal Information described above, we may share your information with third parties with your consent.

## International Data Transfers

We may transfer Personal Information to countries other than the country in which the data was originally collected. These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to help prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account. We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using techniques reasonably designed to secure the information. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store, Personal Information or otherwise.

In certain jurisdictions, we will retain your information only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which the information was collected, depending on the purposes for which the information was collected, the nature of the information, any contractual relationship we may have with you, and our legal or regulatory obligations. We will then destroy your information or anonymize the information for statistical and analytical purposes in accordance with applicable law.

## What Information of Mine Can I Access?

If you are a registered user, you can access information associated with your Account by logging into the Services. Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.

## How Can I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing [hello@buzzslate.com](mailto:hello@buzzslate.com). If you terminate your Account, any information you provided will no longer be accessible via your Account. However, given the nature of sharing on the Services, any public activity on your Account prior to deletion will remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public.

## What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

This Privacy Policy also explains the privacy choices you have when using the Services, including with respect to cookies, marketing emails, targeted advertising, location data and the sharing of your information by BuzzSlate.

You can use many of the features of the Services without registering, thereby limiting the types of Personal Information that we collect.

You can delete your Account by emailing [mail@hello@buzzslate.com](mailto:hello@buzzslate.com). Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible.

To the extent permitted by applicable law, you may withdraw any consent you previously provided to us, or object at any time on legitimate grounds, to the processing of your Personal Information by contacting us at [hello@buzzslate.com](mailto:hello@buzzslate.com). We will apply your preferences going forward. In some circumstances, withdrawing your consent to BuzzSlate’s use or disclosure of your Personal Information will mean that you will no longer be able to use BuzzSlate products or services.

In certain jurisdictions in which we operate, you may have the right under applicable law to: obtain confirmation that we hold personal information about you, request access to and receive information about the personal information we maintain about you, receive copies of the personal information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information, object to the processing of your personal information, provide instructions for the use of your personal information after death, request to be deleted any personal information collected at the time you qualified as a minor under applicable law, and have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate. The right to access personal information may be limited. To exercise these rights, please contact us as set forth below.

## What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time and without prior notice to you. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Services and, in certain circumstances, seeking your consent.

## What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send us a detailed message to [hello@buzzslate.com](mailto:hello@buzzslate.com).

## Cookies on Foxvibes

BuzzSlate. (“we”, “our” or “us”) uses cookies, web beacons and similar technologies (collectively, “cookies”) on [www.buzzslate.com](https://www.buzzslate.com/about) (the “Site”) to function effectively. This Cookie Notice provides you with information about the cookies used on the Site, their purpose, and the choices you can make with regard to the use of cookies.

### WHAT ARE COOKIES?

Cookies are pieces of text that may be placed on your computer’s hard drive through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Site, share our content, and otherwise use our services through the Internet. A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, is used to transmit information back to a web server.

### TYPES OF COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY WE USE ON THE SITE

**•  Essential Cookies**  
We use essential cookies for the duration of each session (“session cookies”). Session cookies are essential to enable you to securely access the Site and its functionalities. Session cookies are deleted when you log out of the Site or when you close your web browser. The following information may be collected through session cookies: single sign-on data and session ID (to remember your credentials over the course of your session); server affinity and authentication data (to establish and maintain the communication with the most appropriate servers).

Session cookies are also used by us or our service providers to determine whether you have viewed this Cookie Notice to allow for the frequency capping of the cookie on-site notice (an on-site cookie notice at the bottom of the landing page that informs you that cookies are used on the Site and how to enable and disable them). In addition, we use session cookies to remember the choices you make on the Site. You may reject or disable session cookies by altering the cookie function of your browser. The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave cookies active, because they enable you to take advantage of the most attractive features of our services.

**•  Advertising Cookies**  
Third party cookies listed in the Cookie Consent Tool are used for web advertising purposes, such as to understand your use of the Site and your online activities, and to present you with relevant BuzzSlate offers and advertisements tailored to your interests, including on the basis of your selected country or language. We also partner with ad networks that use web beacons to customize relevant content to you on third-party websites. These partnerships allow ad networks to use web beacons enable ad networks to serve targeted BuzzSlate content and advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad networks’ servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies to provide the BuzzSlate content and advertisements, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

Advertising cookies collect the following information: unique identification assigned to your device; IP address; device and browser type; operating system; referring URLs; content viewed or other actions taken on the Site; time and date of those actions; and country information.

**•  Performance Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Third-party persistent cookies, as well as web beacons, are used for web analytics purposes for our exclusive use; i.e., for managing and improving the performance and design of the Site. In addition, to increase the effectiveness of ad delivery, we may deliver a web beacon from an ad network to you through the use of our services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers.

The following information is placed in/collected through the persistent cookies and web beacons: unique identification number assigned to your device; IP address; browser type; operating system; referring URLs; information on actions taken; and dates and times of Site visits. All data collected by third-party cookies on our behalf is aggregated and of a statistical nature.

**Effective Date: 07/02/19**
